vbulletin-mods.co.uk 2016-01-29

# vBulletin-Mods.com Forum - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how http://vbulletin-mods.co.uk uses and protects any information that you give http://vbulletin-mods.co.uk when you use this website. 

http://vbulletin-mods.co.uk is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

http://vbulletin-mods.co.uk may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 20/07/2012. 

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * Contact information including email address
  * IP addresses

**What we do with the information we keep**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * Account recovery.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we keep online. 

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use account cookies to keep you logged into your account and grant you the ability to browse our forum as a full member. Without cookies, this is not possible to do. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
